You see, there, I really have the entire embryonic journey of development number one.
ほら、そこには発生の胚性経路が一番よく表れている。
Pronephros, mesonephros, metanephros.
前腎、中腎、後腎。
So here, I am led into a transgenerational thing in her.
だから、ここでは、彼女の世代を超えたものに導かれている。
Here, this is my primary respiration.
これは私の一次呼吸だ。
What I feel here is a left-right differential shift and compression.
ここで感じるのは、左右の差動的なずれと圧縮だ。
-right.
-右。
This is the movement that appears.
それが現れる動きだ。
Second level that I propose to you in practice, on the back.
実践で提案する2番目のレベルは、仰向けだ。
This time, I take the sacrum.
今回は仙骨を取る。
I don't take the coccyx or the fist.
尾骨や拳は取らない。
I really take my sacrum in hand.
本当に仙骨を手に取る。
There, I take a kidney.
そこで、私は腎臓を一つ取る。
I can imagine taking both like that.
このように両方取ることも想像できる。
But there, I take a kidney, here, in this practice, here.
しかし、ここでは、この実践では、ここで腎臓を一つ取る。
And my first information, is that normally, in this motility movement,
そして私の最初の情報は、通常、この運動性の中で、
the kidney becomes a fulcrum and it is the sacrum that...
腎臓が支点となり、仙骨が...
joins the kidney, so I already know from that, I can already say that there is
腎臓に
something
消化器系か神経系のどちらかに何かがあると言える。だから、そこには
something either at the digestive level or at the neuronal level, so there is
おそらく腹膜のレベルで行う作業があるだろう。私にとっては解放されるだろう。
a work that I will do at the peritoneal level, probably liberated for me
私の感覚では、ここで子宮の磁場の中で子宮レベルの何かを解放するだろう。
in my feeling here, I would go liberate something at the uterine level in the
子宮の磁場の中で。
magnetic field of the uterus.
私はここに、この腎臓の上に身を置く。
I put myself here, on this kidney.
そして、あなたは両方を意識している。
And you are aware of both.
両方を意識している、はい。
I am aware of both, yes.
子宮は本当に集中だ。
The uterus is really a concentration.
だから、それは非常に強力な情報を含んでいる。
So it contains very powerful information,
遠くから感じなければならない。
which we must feel at a distance.
大動脈はそうする。
The aortas do that,
そしてシステムはそうする。
and the system does that.
だから、それは外旋だ。
So it's an external rotation.
内旋。
Endo-rotation.
あなたの地理的な行動に関して。
In relation to your geographical action.
だから、彼らは少しずつ回転し続ける。
So they continue to turn, little by little,
彼らの場所を見つけるまで、そこで彼らは輸出できる。
until they find their place, where they can export themselves.
だから、それは同時に、それだ。しかし、だからこそ、最初はそれほどではないが、
So it's both, that's it, but that's why at the beginning, there isn't so much, but
特に最後には、この動き、背中の回転がある。なぜなら、そこでは大動脈はそれほど強力ではないからだ。
it's especially at the end that I have this movement, in the back rotation, since there, the aortas are not so powerful.
私は、このように空虚さに打ちのめされ、この認識に打ちのめされた。
that I felt, it brought me back, telling me, "Hey, this is something I recognize in my
私が感じたことは、私を連れ戻し、これは私の記憶の中で認識しているものだ、と言わせました。
memory, which is perhaps a problem in the generation, I don't know, and so I'm just going to connect
おそらく世代間の問題かもしれませんが、それは分かりません。だから、私はただそれに接続し、
to that and I'm going to let it.
それを手放します。
primary respiration worked when I did that I told myself there is
一次呼吸が機能したとき、私はこれを行い、まだ終わっていない何かがあると感じました。そして、私は子宮の概念に向かいました。
something that is not finished and I went towards this notion of uterus if
子宮の概念に向かいました。子宮はそこにはありませんが、だからといってエネルギーがないわけではありません。
you want which is not there but that's not why the energy is not there a
集中力。だから私にとっては、まだ助けられる何かがあります。
concentration so for me there is something that can still help
だから、ここに空虚さが生まれると、それはそこに現れるでしょう。あるいは、人々はエネルギーを首に転送します。
that's why it creates a void here well it will manifest there or then the
人々は首にエネルギーを転送します。
people transfer their energy to the neck
わかりますか？それはそうします。
simple practice, very rebalancing because it is an articulation between the ecto
これは非常にバランスを整えるシンプルなプラクティスです。なぜなら、それは外胚葉と
and the endo.
内胚葉の間の関節だからです。
And so you play on an intermediate tissue, you see, you just play on a tissue that is there to
だから、あなたは中間組織に作用しているのです。あなたは、そこにある組織に作用しているのです。
help you, in fact, it helped me a lot in my practice to rebalance a sacrum, to
実際、それは私の実践において、仙骨のバランスを整え、再調整するのに非常に役立ちました。
rework it, it helped a lot, I take the whole sacrum in hand, okay, and I come to
それは非常に役立ちました。私は仙骨全体を手に取り、腎臓の領域に
the level of
腎臓の領域に
the renal lodge like this, I put myself on the microcrystalline field, so I keep the unity of the body.
このように腎臓の領域に手を置きます。私は微結晶の場に身を置きます。つまり、私は体の統一性を保ちます。
Each time I tell myself, Mark,
毎回、私は自分に言い聞かせます。
take back the unity, take back the unity, take back the unity.
統一性を取り戻せ、統一性を取り戻せ、統一性を取り戻せ。
Because we tend to be on the feeling of our hands.
なぜなら、私たちは自分の手の感覚に集中しがちだからです。
I always take this globality and I take the space around.
私は常にこの全体性を捉え、周囲の空間を捉えます。
Always this notion of space.
常にこの空間の概念。
And my neutral, and I wait little by little for the neutral to emerge.
そして私のニュートラル、そして私はニュートラルが少しずつ現れるのを待ちます。
Here, there is a health that expresses itself, there is something that comes,
ここには健康が表現されており、何かが来ていますが、
but it's as if we can't go all the way.
しかし、最後まで行けないようなものです。
It's as if, well, I haven't finished.
まるで、ほら、終わっていないかのようなものです。
It's someone who is on the path, who has started and who, we
それは、道を歩んでいる人、旅を始めた人であり、私たちは
advance step by step, we are a little lazy.
一歩一歩進んでいますが、少し怠惰です。
If I say that, it puts her back on the path, it remotivates the kidney, I
もし私がそう言うなら、それは彼を道に戻し、腎臓を再活性化させます。私は
feel that.
それを感じます。
There, there is a process that has started, there is still a brake that
ほら、そこにプロセスが始まりました。まだブレーキがかかっています。
comes here, you see, it goes down well, it lengthens on everything that is on the right side,
ここに来て、ほら、それはよく下がり、右側全体に伸びています。
but to the right.
右側に。
and still a little and to the left up to the left and still a little little
そして、もう一つ小さな、そして左上にもう一つ小さな、小さな
catch so I
引っかかりがあります。だから私は
put myself I saw it I don't leave so I
私はそれを見ました。私は離れません。だから私はそれを
put it in the primary respiration and I am patient it is
一次呼吸に入れ、忍耐強く待ちます。
me who becomes patient when it goes down here it turns like that so
私が忍耐強くなります。それがここに下がってくると、このように回転します。
if I take here clockwise
だから、もし私がここを時計回りに取ると、
the other one will make me counter-clockwise it's a movement
もう一方は反時計回りになります。それは動きです。
where in fact it opens towards the front
実際には前方に開いています
like that okay the anterior face will look towards the back it will develop
このように、前方が背中の方を向くようになります。
there there is not yet
まだ発達していません
a renal hilum there is not yet a renal hilum since the renal hilum will
まだ腎臓はありません。まだ腎臓はありません。なぜなら腎臓は
be developed in
中に発達するからです
metanephros but it received
後腎ですが、彼は受け取りました
This movement, if you will.
この動きは、もしあなたが望むなら。
It's a movement a bit in torsion, like that, you see.
それは少しねじれた動きです、このように、わかりますか。
Since the mesoaortas, here, are not up there.
なぜなら、ここにある中動脈は上にはないからです。
So, it's from the thoracic region that it will form much more, you see.
したがって、それは胸部領域からずっと多く形成されるでしょう、わかりますか。
So, I first have my blastema.
だから、まず私の芽があります。
There, it disappears, it induces the whole system.
そこで、それは消え、システム全体を誘導します。